Boom!
Hi.
Hello. Good morning.
Good morning.
It's 7:00 in the morning.
Wow, that's early!
I'm at Sendai Station, where the Nogizaka46 Manatsu no Kokusai Tour Miyagi Concert was held until yesterday!
Thank you very much.
Oh, I'm sorry I'm late.
You're welcome to join us.
No, no, no!
We'll bring you two cheerful people in the morning.
We did it!
Well, we are...
In fact, this time, in conjunction with Miyagi Park...
JR Sendai Station...
And Sendai Station...
They made Sendai Station so much fun.
Did you see that?
Did you see it?
I saw it.
You really saw it?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I saw it.
I saw it because I had to.
We decided to go home after seeing it.
And we're in a bullet train car, right?
You did it, didn't you?
Not so fast, right?
We did that too.
I'm just saying, let's listen to the music while we go home.
Oh, wow! That's great!
But, you know, my voice is kind of dry.
But, you know, it's early in the morning.But now, you see, it's early in the morning.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
I'm not thirsty.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, so...
I'm gonna be honest with you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're right. You're early.
You know what?
Yesterday, yesterday we did the show.
Today we start filming at 7:00 a.m. That's early.
That's right.
But it's a self-explanatory district.
We woke you up at 6:00 a.m., right?
That's right. 6:00 a.m., right on time.
We stamped each other's names.
That's why I'm fine.
But they're up and they're fine.
We're both fine. We're both fine in the morning.
We're gonna work hard.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And we don't have much time before the bullet train, so...
Wow, it's so bright
Dazzling
You're here.
Thank you, so
Thank you for lighting us up
Wow, this is great.
God is cheering you on.
Yeah, I know.
Well, let's, uh...
Let's go, let's go, right? Well, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Where are we going?
- Where are you going?- Today, you don't have an aikobun, do you?
- It's okay.
- It's this morning with the concept of silkworm blue and all that.
- Of course it is.
- What kind of promise are you making this morning?
I'm gonna have to get a little prettier.
Isn't this amazing? Travel bookmark map.
Look at this map.
It's a map of all the places I've visited in my travel bookmarks.
I've been to so many places!
Wait, you can go there too!
Yes, Shiori, this way too!
Shiori, you can go this way, too!
Mayu, show us.
Mayu, this one, this one.
Mayu-chan, this one.
I've got to pick one, now.
This one
I like this one.
It's great. Thank you.
Is Shiori here?
I want you to do the same pose, that's... oh, wait, Shiori's here.
I want to do the same pose.
What? Why? You want to do it.
It's embarrassing.
Embarrassing.
Well, show it to Shiori and have her take a look.
I'll look for Mayu.
Is it mine?
Why?
Shiori.
Shiori's singing so hard.
Where are you going?
Oh, here it comes, here it comes!Oh, here they come!
There's the blue-green cocoon.
Look, it's good.
And there's the last bookmark, too.
Boiled eggs!
Sasuchan's starting to think so, too.
But you're a little black here.
Or maybe it's just her black hair.
I don't know...
Ha-ha-ha.
A little...
And Yumeki's face.
Dreamy.
Why did you choose this picture?
You don't stand out.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
She's cute.
Hey...
I like her hair.
Really?
It's like a laser beam.
It's so miso.
Look at this.
Yeah.
Yumeki did it...
Yumeki did this amazing miso thing, Koichan did this, and Rei-chan did this...
If you turn it this way, it'll all be covered.
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
Amazing miso!
That's too much!
Look, the products are so good!
This is the third one I've found.
I don't get it.
Is that always the cuckoo dancing in the background?
Kakki's perfect... the third one.
The third one is perfect.It looks perfect.
Where can I dance?
There's this great exhibit.
There's a panel of the members at the station. Let's go look for it.
Oh, you want to go look for them?
By the way, that was me yesterday.
The day before yesterday.
I found a camera and, you know, took down the notification tone.
Oh, no!
How did you find it?
How did you find it? I found it by accident.
Wow, it just happens, doesn't it?
Close, close, close.
It happens sometimes.
Koi, you're always so small and Oru-chan's voice is so far away.
My ears are too close now.
Too close, too close.
I was talking directly to your brain.
Yes, I was talking directly to you.
Too much!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Why all at once?
What are you doing?
It's loosening up.
It's coming back.
Just a little bit.
Oh, my God.
Maybe it's...
He's taking it from the edge. - He's taking it from the edge.
He's filming from the edge, and I wasn't the only one.
He's filming each and every one of them from the edge.
That was kind of sweet.
Hey, it was kind.
It was, you know, we were...Here's what we're going to do.
Shinkansen train announcements.
Say you're having it filmed.
I'm going to film two cars.
Wow, that's something for me.
They gave me some love.
I don't know, and it's got our signatures on it, too. He gave me some love!
And our autographs are written on it, too.
And Mayu-tan is in Osaka area.
And Shiori is in Miyagi and Fukushima, Tohoku area.
I'm so happy!
And I'm making an announcement!
It's nice to hear it from the phone.
You don't mind?
Before that...
There's a Hi-Q Beagle.
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
Can I go somewhere else?
We're not showing the Hi-Q Beagle.
Can I just go check it out for a second?
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'll be waiting for you.
Wait, I want to cackle for you.
I want to give you a gourd.
I want to give you a gourd, I want to give you a gourd.
Does that mean they're dating?
Oh my God.
Are they dating?
Why would three third graders be dating?
Oh my God.
There's too much going on.
Asahi's drinking a Ramune.
He's drinking a Ramune.
The way he's holding it.How to hold it
Long fingers
Like a recorder
So cool!
What is a recorder like?
I have Tam's panel.
It's like I have my own panel.
Tam-chan's panel
Tam-chan's panel.
It's out of alignment.
Why?
You're really intense today.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
They really don't like me.
I don't hate you.
But you're so high-strung.
I mean...
Not many people are watching.
Yeah, maybe more than before.
She's still on.
Maybe you've seen her before.
Is he tiny?
Oh, there it is!
I've got it!
I'm here.
Wasn't there?
Yes, I was.
Yes, I'll put it on the screen.
Thank you very much.
This is my care.
Yes.
This is my congratulations.
That's great.
What's that? You're shining.
Why is the light so great?
It's like this.It's pointed like this.
Why?
Oh, it's so pretty over there.
This one's prettier. This one's prettier.
Yeah, it's prettier this way.
Oh, yeah?
Is it?
Shanayanans.
I'm going to listen to some shanayanans.
I wonder if the voices are in this one.
I'm sure.
I hear this rattling sound.
What do you think?
This guy was recording the whole thing.
No way... let's use different voices.
Okay.
That's great.
I should never have said that.
No way.
You know what?
I can't help it if it really came out last time.
It's bad.
It's really bad.
No way!
Thank you for using JR East today!
Just now...
My...
I went to the place where the panel was.
When I went there...
I heard
Announcement.
No, it wasn't.
I heard you saw this in the middle.
But... But...Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What? No, no, no, no.
Sorry. Sorry.
Huh? Sorry. No. No. No.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry. Please watch this press conference. We would like to ask a favor of our customers.
To keep customers waiting for two people,
To leave your luggage,
Please use it until waiting.
We ask our customers to use this room.
We do not want you to be waiting for us,
We will wait for you from the time you check in.
Please take your time. We are not on time, so please be on time, please be on time, please be on time.
It's not the time, so it's not the time.
In time, in time, in time
Please give us your time.
Please give us your time and we will give you our time.
In time, in time, in time
In your time
In your time, in your time, in your time
You're the one who speaks without saying a word, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow...
I'm the one who's been listening to you for the last five years.
They're listening to my voice on the Tohoku Shinkansen.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
When I went there...
I heard Shiori-chan's announcement.
Shiori-chan's voice appeared in the announcement.
No, no, no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no.
What? I'm sorry. - No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Speak for yourself.Speak up for yourself
listen to the voice of the world
Listen with a good voice
simply and always surely
what is it?
And the dungeon
You have to speak properly
But Shu-chan's voice is like that.
I'm going to talk.
If you've been listening to me for a while...
You sound a little funny.
I don't know...
It's a little bit normal.
That's the kind of narrator I'm talking about.
It's a nice voice, isn't it?
I mean...
She's got hair, too.
I don't know...
Announcement.
What's that? Maybe it's not me.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
But...
You always have a grown-up voice.
Always.
I'm not fully awake anymore.
I know it's me, but it's like that.
Listen to the way she talks.
"Gah!
Don't twist it.
Not twisted.
No, you know what? You know what I mean?
You know, the announcer..,
I don't know.
I don't know. I mean, the announcer's voice is very different,So, that's a crazy announcement,
Oh, okay.
All right, then.
What do you think? It's blue. It's good. Oh! Oh, man, let's go.
Oh! How did it go, Mr. Oh?
Good.
Comfortable.
Huh!
It wasn't a man's world.
Mm-hmm
Comfortable clothes
YouTube
Thank you for using JR East!
This is the Tohoku Shinkansen Yamahiko bound for Tokyo.
Next stop is Fukushima.
Can I let you know that too?
Now?
Right now?
Is it coming?
Can we have a look around?
Can we just take a look around?
Okay.
I'm standing up now.
This is what's going on behind the scenes of the installation.
Here's where you can ask questions.
Members asking questions, things like that.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
This train is
Tohoku Shinkansen Yamamiko No. Please, please, please, please do not interfere with the use of caution customers and handrails. We appreciate your cooperation.
How was it?
Perfect.
Lovely.
Lovely. The voice of perfection.
But my run won't be over soon.But my run won't be over soon.
Oh, my! That's a lot of traffic. That's something.
That's great.
Who's got the girl's seat?
Kakki!
Kakki! Our Kakki!
I'm in the Grand Palace.
Ah! It's Jackie! It's Kakki!
Thank you for using JR East.
This train is the Tohoku Shinkansen bound for Tokyo at Nagamiko Port.
We don't want large luggage to move in the building.
Please do not place large luggage in a way that it cannot be moved or reflown in the building.
Please be considerate.
It's a river.
I'll take it.
Oh, my God.
Too good!
Cokes of cheese... and the last of the scorch.
Not hungry?
Dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty...
This is the Tohoku Shinkansen bound for Yamami Kojima, Tokyo.
The next stop is Utsunomiya.
We'll be staying in Utsunomiya.
That's right, we're eating gold leaf while listening to the voice of the faraway land.
I've never heard of it.
I don't know.
Haruka's cute!
Just hearing her voice is cute.
I may have mentioned it somewhere...
I was on the bullet train.
On the bullet train...
I was on the bullet train once.
On the way back on the bullet train.
I saw the concert...After the concert...
He said he was going to take the bullet train.
At first, it was normal.
But then I thought I'd be arriving in Tokyo soon.
I said, "How much longer?
She's...
She's usually so tense with me.
Because I'm so uptight about her.
I don't know...
It's just...
She's poking me on the shoulder... because I'm so set on her... but there's something about her, isn't there?
It's like...
Like this.
Are you conscious? In your sleep?
I don't know.
I was like, "I'm sleepy.
Hmm? And then...
You know...
Your hand.
What?
We're dating. I'm sorry.
That's not good.
And then I said, "Okay, I'm sleeping.
And then I said, "Okay, I'm sleeping. With one hand.
With one hand.
Sleeping peacefully.
When we get there, tell him we're here.
And say thank you.
I see.
Thank you for using JR East.
That's a little voice, isn't it?
This train is bound for Tokyo on the Tohoku Shinkansen Sanyo High School Line.
Next stop is Omiya.
More people will be coming soon.
In a very cute voice!
Thank you for using JR East... and please cooperate with us in making your trip more pleasant... by listening to this special broadcast... from Saitama Prefecture.Thank you for using JR East.
This special broadcast was made by Mayu Tamura, a member of Nogizaka46, from Saitama Prefecture.
Why all the forgiveness?
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
We look forward to seeing you on the next Tohoku Shinkansen.
From Tokyo, I am Mizuki Yamashita of Mugizaka 46.
When Ms. Yamamoto was filming, you know, that voice.
When we were filming.
I was listening to it.
It was right next to the time of the shoot.
I thought it was playing like this.
That's great.
I'm listening to this live.
Sorry, guys.
I, uh... when I was actually filming this...
I told you that I heard this when I was actually filming.
Well, where did you hear it?
Well, um...
I'm talking to you as we're filming, or I'm talking to you live.
I heard it.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, guys.
So tell me the truth.
I'm listening to everything.
That's right.
I heard the biting part, too.
That was cute.
Haruka heard it too.
Haruka also asked about Yamapeko's bite, which was cute.
She said Kanda's cute too.
I'm sorry.
You were expecting a sleeping cut, right?
She's sleeping... in a cute country.
You're a woman who adjusts herself.You're a woman who adjusts herself.
Do you want to turn around on my shoulder?
What? Which one do you want?
Down?
Okay, let's do it, shall we?
Okay, here we go.
He's laughing.
I'm serious.
I'm gonna hide it with my hair.
You're gonna disappear? No, I'll probably be hidden by my hair, so I'm not really disappearing now, am I? You're not gonna disappear for real?
Hey, can you be serious?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can you do that for me?
Can you do it?
Oh, wait a minute, okay.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I don't know.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Is it white? Are you...
I'm white?
But it's today.
Did you know?
The maser is white.
That's right.
I'm proud of myself to begin with.
I stuck my thumb in it.
I got sucked into this hole.
Don't stick your thumb in it.
Don't even... don't even... don't stick your thumb in there.
Don't stick your thumb in this hole
It's white and I hit it and it's like...
I've got it stuck in me...
Thumb.Thumb
Thumb
I hate my thumb.
There you go.
They're gonna use that.
They're gonna use it.
If you point your thumb, it'll break.
Bite my finger.
I hate it when they bite my fingers... And that's it, we're almost at the end of the line, Tokyo.
Take care.
As a live performance
Lance in the Shinkansen
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much.
How was it?
The show was great.
Like this.
The bullet train.
And you're going to do it on campus.
I had that kind of feeling.
I was very happy.
I hope we can do something like this again next year.
I'll try my best to see something every time.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
I had a great time you two, let's do it again.
bye bye